<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!DOCTYPE foo [
<!ELEMENT foo ANY >
<!ENTITY file SYSTEM "file://index.php" >
]>
<hero id="1">
    <details>
        <name>&file;</name>
        <img>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/mobile-legends/images/e/e6/Steel_Sweetheart.jpg</img>
        <tag>Steel Sweetheart</tag>
        <quotes>Hop aboard. Well, it's my job to protect honey bear.</quotes>
        <role>Fighter</role>
        <specialty>Charge | Burst</specialty>
        <lane>EXP lane</lane>
        <release>January, 2018</release>
        <durability>90</durability>
        <offense>80</offense>
        <skill_effects>70</skill_effects>
        <difficulty>80</difficulty>

        <stats>
            <hp>2658</hp>
            <mana>430</mana>
            <hp_regen>7.8</hp_regen>
            <mana_regen>16</mana_regen>
            <physical_attack>119</physical_attack>
            <magic_power>0</magic_power>
            <physical_defense>24</physical_defense>
            <magic_defense>15</magic_defense>
            <attack_speed>1.12</attack_speed>
            <movement_speed>255</movement_speed>
            <attack_speed_percentage>100%</attack_speed_percentage>
        </stats>

        <hero_feature>He is a front-line fighter hero who can throw an enemy or an ally to assist. Combining with significant CC and very high damage, he is a very effective hero in the heat of battle. Sustained damage single-target Fighter. Can throw enemy units to attack, or throw allies to assist.</hero_feature>
    </details>

    <abilities>
        <passive>
            <name>Mecha Suppression</name>
            <img>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/mobile-legends/images/6/6f/Smart_Missiles.png</img>
            <detail>Each time Jawhead deals damage to a target, Jawhead inflicts a stack of Compression for 3 seconds that can stack up to 10 times.</detail>
        </passive>
        <first_skill>
            <name>Smart Missiles</name>
            <img>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/mobile-legends/images/6/6f/Smart_Missiles.png</img>
            <detail>Jawhead enters Launch State where his body-mounted missiles randomly fires up to 12 times.</detail>
        </first_skill>
        <second_skill>
            <name>Ejector</name>
            <img>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/mobile-legends/images/c/c4/Ejector.png</img>
            <detail>Jawhead enters Fling State, gaining 30% Movement Speed and a shield that absorbs 350 / 440 / 530 / 620 / 710 / 800 (+140% Total Physical Attack) damage for 5 seconds.</detail>
        </second_skill>
        <ultimate_skill>
            <name>Unstoppable Force</name>
            <img>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/mobile-legends/images/5/58/Unstoppable_Force.png</img>
            <detail>Jawhead locks onto an enemy hero, charging to them and dealing 350 / 475 / 600 (+150% Total Physical Attack) Physical Damage to the target and stunning them. Surrounding units will also be knocked back and take the same amount of damage.</detail>
        </ultimate_skill>
    </abilities>

    <story>
        <background>
        <![CDATA[
            Clandestine organizations have existed throughout many ages of the Land of Dawn's history. No one knows the true purpose of these organizations, but one thing is for sure, whenever a crisis is in hand, one of their mysterious creations emerge from the shadows to restore order to the world.<br><br>
            Professor Henry and his wife worked for the Dawn Council, known for its research in cutting-edge technology, and providing an endless and varied stream of high-tech products to government agencies and mysterious, anonymous clients. But, when they finally finished developing their manually operated robot, SMART-01, all this changed. Their new creation was more intelligent and powerful than any android robot the world had seen before and was also designed, such that once a genetically matched host controlled it, it could act according to the controller's consciousness.<br><br>
            The leader of the Dawn Council saw the potential of this technology, for warfare and ordered the Henry's to transfer the technology to the selected government agencies for a mass production program. The Henry's refused. After ordering their Prototype SMART-01 to destroy all of the experimental data, the Henrys mysteriously disappeared.<br><br>
            To this day, little Ailee had no knowledge of these events, however, after her parents went missing, she had been targeted by the Dawn Council, as an important hostage. To obtain the truth behind the Henry's disappearance, the scientists of the Dawn Council barged into the Henry's house and violently tried to seize Ailee. However, Ailee managed to evade these bad people and dashed out of her house. As Ailee ran ahead of the chasing mob of scientists, she remembered, what her father had once told her: "Remember Ailee, when there is no way out, press the button on your pocket watch and think hardly of me and the guardian will show up to protect you". Ailee did just as her father had told her to, and asked for her father for help, as she ran, her little legs barely able to move any longer, when all of a sudden a big box dropped between her and her pursuers. The box had an inscription: GUARDIAN CLASS-1.<br><br>
            A powerful beam split apart the box and from within, emerged the robot SMART-01. Ailee's heart beat faster as it walked up to her and scanned her face. Recognizing her to be a VIP host, SMART-01 engaged Guardian mode on Ailee. Then looking around at the mad scientists, SMART-01 activated it's Elimination mode. The people tried to attack SMART-01, but it released a flurry of missiles and grenades, turning every one of them, but Ailee, to ash.<br><br>
            She understood the true power of SMART-01, also realizing that there were secret gears hidden inside this pocket watch. She wondered if it might hold any clues to find her parents. She turned to SMART-01 and gave her next order, commanding the robot to help her find her parents with the help of this pocket watch. SMART-01 scanned the pocket watch with his inbuilt sensors, and indicated three possible locations.<br><br>
            After the passage of these events, all she knew and cared about was that this special robot had always been there to protect and accompany her. SMART-01 occasionally calls her Honeybear, just like her father did, while she affectionately calls him Jawhead, in return. Finally, with the support of Jawhead, Ailee gathered enough courage and decided to journey with her robot friend to track down her parent's whereabouts, deciding that she would be much stronger when she would meet her parents, the next time.
        ]]>
        </background>
    </story>
</hero>
